Dear Honorable Judge,
hello
Litigation for division of shared property
This is plaintiff Song Ha-kyung.
The judge said about the impeachment
How much do you know?
You probably have no idea
I am a lawyer
I haven't seen anyone who lives here.
I guess it's because it's near the DMZ, right?
Hey, Dr. Song.
- Hello
- Have a nice trip.
Huh?
Pacheon is
The first thing after a war
It has a nickname: a place to die.
But I
Every day is already a war
Oh my, number 18
Oh, I wasn't swearing.
I should introduce bus number 18.
Departure interval: 40 minutes
There are five villages in the province.
There are only 18 seats
Ah...
11 years ago
I added it when I was 18
Huh? Hey, the bus is coming!
evil!
Departure interval: 80 minutes
There are ten villages in the province.
Sir!
Uh, uh, uh, driver!
I am ready to die
If you don't jump into the driveway
I couldn't catch the village bus
sorry
Baekdo, what are you doing? Hurry up and get in
Like this
Risking my life every day
This is where you have to go to school
The northernmost village in Pacheon-si
This is Patan-myeon.
ride
Patan-myeon for 17 years
slowly
Make me a character wrecker
I made it
“Daeungjeon”
speak up
you go away
Let's never see each other again
I am Patan-myeon
I really hate it
Take me from this cursed land
If you can help me escape
No accidents will happen in the future
No complaints whatsoever
I will live peacefully
Dear Judge,
Please break this broken man’s heart.
Please count.
Dear guests
I'll land in a moment
Please fasten your seat belt
thank you
♪ Ruin ♪
♪ You really ignored me ♪
♪ There are no bribes for us ♪
♪ I can't go looking for you ♪
♪ Ruin ♪
Patan-myeon
Administrative collapse, wake up!
Awaken! Wake up!
- Hey, Director Song.
- Yes?
The old chairman out there
Are you your father’s elementary school classmate?
Uh, to be precise.
Senior citizen association secretary
Father's cousin's brother's
Are you an elementary school classmate?
That’s perfect, Director Song.
Please stop those old people.
My ears are noisy too
I can't work because the speed is noisy.
If you are going to use your academic background,
The mayor uses it, right?
The mayor is also a senior.
Didn't you do it?
Hey, come on!
Those instructions are exactly what I
After 14:00
I think it can be done
Until 14:00 today
Submit this report
The mayor said that.
But today at 14:00
A reporter from Domin Ilbo is coming.
So the report is urgent?
Is that urgent?
Then
I have until 14:00
If I let them go home
The mayor told me
What would you like me to do for you?
Oh, it's a deal again, right?
Oh, it's noisy
Okay, whatever I ask you to do
call
Tilt it! Tilt it!
Tilt...
No, ten times
The mayor is coming out
Why is Dr. Song here?
- I'll share it with you.
- Yes
Okay, let's take this one by one.
Please share back and forth
I'll share it with everyone.
Now, if you have severe myopia,
The handout you just received
Also, if you have severe farsightedness, click here.
Please look at the blackboard.
Just follow along.
'Number 1'
‘Search for Pacheon City Hall in the search bar.’
'Number 2
Go to the Pacheon City Hall website.
'Number 3'
‘Click on the complaint window at the top left’
'No. 4, bottom right
Click ‘Write’
The last 'number 5'
‘Write a complaint.
'Press the submit button at the bottom'
Do you understand?
No, the chief saw it.
What if I erase it completely?
We don't know anything about the Internet
They seem to think they are people.
This is shooting straight at city hall.
How can the mayor not do it?
Higher than the mayor
The mayor will see it.
Oh, if it's a market
It’s the mayor **bung, huh?
So, is the market going to punish you for this?
hmm?
You came dressed so nicely today.
Our persimmon tree house grandmother
and
An elderly person from a tile-roofed house also came here.
Hello, Director of Baduk Academy
Old man in stone wall house
Also, the owner of our crab restaurant
And my middle school in Ochon Dangsuk.
Even my classmate Song Jae-geun
Hey, I've been in this neighborhood for 17 years.
Who put up those streetlights?
I built it when I was in middle school.
Who dressed those wooden clothes?
I wore this when I was in the second year of middle school.
This is all because of complaints like this.
This is what I achieved
Therefore, teachers clearly
you will make it
You can do it!
Okay, shall we go eat now?
Yes, let's go
Well, my stomach needs to be warm.
Or something like that.
- Let's go
- Let's go.
The restaurant is over there
After all, ace is ace
I'm not Dr. Song of Bankruptcy for nothing.
Baby, come join our team, huh?
Aig, please take me with you.
A smart ace on the face
I don't need it
Just don't do anything
Just for 1 person
I need an iron rice bowl
No, but what is it?
fence teardown project
I heard that only the final PT at the headquarters remains?
Ah, yes
Hey
When will it click again?
Did you apply for that business?
Oh my, that's just it
The budget is over 400 million
Should I go to the foreign office?
If I take the job myself...
If it comes
The team leader also made sure to
You are supporting me.
Ah...
Ugh, it's almost lunch time.
Let's go out for lunch
- I will buy it.
- Huh?
Then, how about your mother-in-law’s kimchi stew?
uh, nice there
Ugh, Director Song, in Patan-myeon
Don't you know I'm not buying food?
Is it a day or two?
Enjoy your meal
Enjoy it
Oh, I feel like pretending
Yes, man
Ah, the air
It’s just great, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Hahaha
Heaven helped me, heaven helped me
Now, this is the valley right next to it
Right behind is Patan Mountain.
Perfect for living a healthy life
- Oh, yes.
- You said three generations are living together, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Then just this house
It's just perfect
You'll know just by looking at it.
Oh my
The landlord comes just at that moment.
- Oh my, Dr. Song
- Hello
Ah, our Dr. Song
Our neighborhood is just the best
I am a top civil servant.
level 7
Oh, my young friend has a house.
Just plain dumb, yeah
Uh, ah, come in.
Come in, yeah
Please go in
Now
Come in, come in
It's really spacious, huh?
- Sure.
- Yes
Come on in.
Please come in
- Wow~
- Oh, it's good, right?
Hey, it’s sunny and south facing.
Well, there's nothing to worry about
Since it is a wooden building, the insulation is just good.
Wow, look at this
This interior finish
Something this luxurious
Oh, it's true, huh?
The interior is also really stylish.
Even though it's old, it's clean
This is my parents
You put it all on yourself, one by one.
Won't fall or break
Ah, yes
My father is an architect
You were good with your hands.
Ah, the owner next door
Director Baek is also an architect.
It's sweet because you two are friends
It's a fun house I made to live in.
Ah, that
How long did you say you lived here?
- It's been 17 years.
- Oh, yeah.
Well now
How many people live there?
Uh, for now
I live alone
There have been 10 people in the past.
You probably have enough space.
Huh?
- Oh my.
- child
What kind of dog?
- Take a look
- Oh, it's nice here too.
no
Is this Wardin again?
cute
- Good, right?
- Wow
- What's your name?
- Watermelon
Watermelon, hello
Aw, cute
So
This door and that door
In this house, in that house
It's a place you can come and go, right?
yes
Chatting together in the evening
It would be great as a public space.
- Um
-Who made this?
Ah
I'm sorry, but you can't touch this.
Would you like to look elsewhere?
I don't have much time
Yes, please come in
Come on in.
Come in
Wow
If you use it as a study room for your kids
That might work, huh?
Hey, the bookshelf is like this
It's all over the wall
Oh, but it seems too thin here.
- Really?
- Ah
This is a space created by erecting a temporary wall.
Although it is thin
Well, there is no problem with insulation
Don't worry about heating costs.
- Ah...
- No, but
What is this?
Ah, what kind of hole is this?
- Ah...
- Oh, here too...
Ah
The son of the white general I mentioned earlier.
Since childhood
We lived next door together.
It just happened while we were arguing at that time.
It looks like a hole
Wow, it was very noisy.
The neighborhood is really noisy
The two stick together...
So now I
Can I ask you a question?
Do you want to renovate and repair this house?
Would you be willing?
Oh no, no
I really need something
I think it would be nice to live like that.
That's right
Are you using it for actual residence?
Are you sure?
Rental accommodation or
A second house or something like that.
Are you planning to change it?
no
our family for a long time
We are looking for a place to live together.
Okay
- Please contact us quickly
- Yes
yes, thank you
Oh, if you contact me too late
I'm not leaving this house
Oh my
Please go in
Oh no
Oh, because it’s an empty house next door.
If you are busy, don't come.
They told me to leave the keys to me.
Oh no
Who do you like?
Should I listen to it, tsk?
Is everything going well with you?
Yes, of course
Ha...
Baek Do-ha, you
Ha-kyung will sell the house.
You're not just going to leave it alone, are you?
So what is your last hand?
Oh well, without that either
Just blindly
I wouldn't have come back
The left side you see now is Patan-myeon.
On the right is Taehwa City.
What is the difference between these two neighborhoods?
-There is no wall?
- That's right
There is no fence in the photo on the right.
After tearing down the wall, Taehwa City
About the size of 55 soccer fields
A green park was created
Solved the parking problem
Thanks to this, the alley was renovated
Even the commercial district has survived.
If we just tear down the wall in Patan-myeon,
Parking complaints disappear
The commercial districts of surrounding villages will also revive.
Then let me ask you a question.
As the Transportation Department
I'm asking
If parking is a problem, try another method.
I think it would be efficient to look for it.
As you know, Patan-myeon is
No parking tower permit.
Because it harms the scenery.
And the parking tower
Rather than building
It takes more budget to tear down the wall.
It costs less and is also efficient.
You just talked about budget.
This is 400 million won
The myeon office is in charge of this.
Isn't this too big a undertaking?
In terms of entrustment,
I don't know if it's a big business, but
not for me
Among the businesses I was in charge of,
This is the smallest
As everyone knows
Yeonjin also started a fence business.
It was discontinued because it was difficult to obtain consent from residents.
You probably know the cases that couldn't be resolved.
Even though the fence is public property
The land is private property, Director Song.
Yes, Chief Jeon Ye-eun of the Department of Architecture.
Thank you for the question I've been waiting for
within a week
I will receive consent from all residents.
It's not that difficult
When I worked at the main office
It's something I've always done
- Oh, yes, Mr. Mayor.
- Why do you want to do this business?
Ah...
I
Living in Patan for 17 years
This is what I wanted to change the most.
As a Patan resident, I
I have been filing complaints for 17 years.
I'm also doing things that I haven't heard of before.
I have a fever
I'm going to change it, Mr. Mayor.
Just before the personnel change
No one will want to do it together
Are you confident?
Yes, I am confident
Well then, there is an answer.
With final approval
Did you say Song Ha-kyung, the chief officer?
yes, that's right
I have high expectations, and again at the main office.
I wish I could see it
thank you
Wow
Yeah
Oh, really?
Are you really accepting all of those conditions?
yes, good
I'll go now, okay
- Hello
- Oh!
- Oh my, welcome.
- Hello
Oh my, Dr. Song
Come this way, come this way
Oh, come on a second.
Why?
With Director Baek
Wasn’t it a good conversation?
yes, that's right
He told me everything
You delegated the right to purchase and sell.
Why?
Ah, that, Major Baek
Did you bring your personal seal?
Sure
Power of attorney and personal seal
Seal stamp certificate
I brought everything.
- Give it to me.
- Here is the power of attorney
seal certificate
‘Baek Ki-ho’, oh my
Director Baek’s name is Baek Ki-ho, right?
Yes, that's right, Baek Ki-ho
Ha...
Huh?
uh?
'Baekdoha'
No, uncle
What does that mean now?
Baek Do-ha is in Seoul now?
Oh, since when?
no
No, that's not important
No, you clearly told me
You said you would leave all the buying and selling to me, right?
But why suddenly
It changed to Baekdoha?
Oh, that's...
No, I want a birthday present.
Come visit me in person
How can I ask for your name?
A birthday present?
He wants me to buy something
The thing you asked for was that ash tree, huh?
That was all I had
What is that guy, the one who is pestering me?
A guy who wants nothing in his life
Why do you want it?
mister!
Ah, Mr. Choi, Mr. Choi, hard hat, hard hat.
Gotta wear a hard hat, uh-uh
Ha-kyung, because you’re busy
Uh, call Doha, huh?
Uh, let's talk later.
W, hello? mister?
Ha...
yes
why am i like this
I wondered if things would work out well.
I forgot for a moment
my summer
I really don't have any luck
Doha guy
I didn't change my phone number, it's the same
If he says what you say, he'll die
Contact me
Ha...
I'm so carefree these days
I just forgot
Jingly and dog-like
about this summer
Yes, it started that day.
In June, I suddenly got hives all over my body.
- Did you find out?
- They say it’s like a peanut allergy.
Ha...
I thought it was food poisoning
In the place I went
I was diagnosed with a peanut allergy...
If everything is better than that
I have somewhere to go with my dad.
From the beginning of June
hitting 37 degrees
Ta-da!
In this amazing place
I came to live
It was the summer when I was 12 years old.
- Peanut restaurant?
- Yes
Dad, daughter is allergic to peanuts
Didn't you hear that there was one?
Hey, the house where two become one, the peanut house
How cute is this? It also has meaning
So we
As for who you're going to live with...
ever since
My bad luck that has continued until now
I can't express it enough
Huh
Please save me, okay?
Really, when I say nice things
Don't you listen? hey!
Ah, it's hot!
Ha...
Ugh! uh!
- ah!
-Are you okay?
iced coffee!
Hey!
Why, why, why, why
Why, why, why
Huh? Why, huh?
this condition
I met a buyer who said everything was okay.
This is luck
He said his wish is to leave bankruptcy.
Dr. Song, are you going to miss this?
uh? uh
Hey, hey, hey!
Ah
Ah...
Ah, sir, ha...
What is it?
"Interesting music"
Wow
I went to the market and found amaranth greens.
Something has already come out, right?
Ah, but while talking on the phone with Song Ha-kyung
I tried it and it tasted a bit salty.
Still, grandpa
On a chopstick of vegetables
You should just eat two spoons of rice at a time.
Kyeong-tae Jeong, sixty-three this year.
- It's clumsy with his hands, but for him...
-Mr...
This time with black rice and nutritious rice.
Ha~
I really am, grandpa
Even gondrena water rice
With grandfather's favorite things
Because I packed a lot
Warm it up well and eat it one by one
in someone's teeth
I'm talking about sweating, really.
Oh, really, grandpa!
Are you going to keep ignoring what I say?
Ha...
Hey, song
my grandfather
Isn’t this really too much?
No, to put it bluntly, I
I haven't committed a mortal sin
My grandfather turns 80 the day after tomorrow.
Ah, sometimes I see you
I think I have a second year of middle school disease.
Well, we've been friends for 60 years.
I also cut myself off from Goijang’s grandfather.
What's wrong with being with me for 5 years?
Well, yakgwaji, whatever.
Song, what am I good at?
Aren’t you going to hold on?
ah! Sir, now you say
Let’s eat some too.
As I check your mood right now
To open up your conversation
I've been talking alone for like 30 minutes.
Hey, this isn't even small talk.
It's time to say it now
Oh, what are you trying to say?
Taking a break like this?
Hey
The ingredients are very fresh and good
It's delicious, eat it first.
If it's your job now
I'm not surprised at all
you at city hall
I wasn't surprised when I got cut, huh?
Yes, with that sharp guy from City Hall
We got involved like that the year before last
Even when things go crazy
- I wasn't surprised at all...
- I contacted Doha Baek.
A few months ago in Seoul
They say you came in?
I'm sure you knew
Seungtaek Oppa Baek Doha
There's no way we won't meet
Oh, no... that...
Baekdo came to Seoul
Baekdo? Wow...
Are you very kind?
You’ve been with Baek Do-ha all this time without me knowing.
Have you been in contact and that's it?
pooh!
ouch!
Ah, just because of Seungtaek oppa.
I've only seen it a few times in Seoul.
I guess so, next to Oh Seung-taek
There was no way there wasn’t gum dew.
What is it?
Well, the three of us gathered together on a make-believe day.
Chewing on me makes our friendship stronger
Chopped, or something like that?
Oh, what do you say? Who chews, Mr.
It's done
blow it all
When did Baek Do-ha come in?
Uncle Atelier
You said you took charge of it?
Really, I'm a bastard, I'm a bastard
I'm not even thirty yet
Hey! This time the article
There is a Seongsu Museum.
That's a deal he designed too
With us
He was a great man of different sizes.
No, what am I, Baekdoga
I'm not doing it because I'm proud.
Oh, I just told my brother
That's all I heard
A familiar face, sometimes
It's also in the article
Hey, honestly, you're doing well.
As soon as I came to Korea last year
I won the architecture award
What did they say this year?
Nobel Prize winner in architecture
Are you aiming for the Pritzker Prize?
So
Why did that popular bastard come here?
Well, I guess it came because it was summer.
When it comes to summer, it’s white.
But
Baek Doha has no feelings for you.
You are still like this
If you say Baekdoha, you will be right.
He doesn't talk about you at all
Yeah?
uh
Do you look like you have no feelings?
That's right
But why are there no feelings?
Is there no answer to whitewashing?
uh?
It won't work if I don't have an answer
I sent it
What did you send?
That poisonous son of a bitch
He said he finally contacted Baekdo.
2 years ago before us
When I declared that I was insulating from the back road
We'll never meet again
I thought there wouldn't be one
What did you call me, brother?
Oh, I'm so curious, really.
- Make a deposit first.
- Huh?
Did you forget our bet?
Will Ha-kyung contact me first?
Will Doha contact you first?
Mr...
Anyway, Song
It doesn't help my life
I deposited 100,000 won.
What is it? Why 100,000 won?
I have to send 100,000 won more
Oppa, stocks are cut in half these days, Mr.
I also sent it reflecting the market price.
It’s straight, right?
Ugh
Ah, but I’m worried.
I feel uneasy for some reason
Oppa, have you heard anything from Byeok-do?
It’s because of Song that Baek came to Korea, right?
What do you know, brother?
Tonight too
Everyone who can't sleep
What is the reason?
It's your brain
Because it works
Then the brain
How does it work?
That's by using more of the five senses.
I remember
Smell, touch, sound
That powerful memory
It remains deeply in our afterimage.
So that I can forget that memory
helpful for sleep
We prepared ASMR
- The sound of cicadas is loud.
- Shall we listen?
It's hot
I'm annoyed, when I'm annoyed, I get angry...
Mr...
Ah, those damn mosquitoes.
Can’t they be obliterated?
Oh, that's right
Should I wait for a heavy rain advisory?
damn rainy season
Oh, I'm on duty tomorrow
When is summer going?
But why did he come? Baekdoha?
Ah, sir!
What's wrong with my memory?
Why isn't this bastard contacting me, tsk?
Ah
Ah, why are you white again?
ah!
huh?
June 5th 19:00, Star Cafe
"Cafe Star"
So, Baekdoha
- You're a lawyer?
- This is Seo Soo-hyuk.
Are you disappointed by my arrival?
No, it can't be
I never thought I would see a lawyer today
I was just a little embarrassed because I didn't know.
People who don't want to see a lawyer
3 content certifications per week
Can you send it to me?
'I will enforce it'
‘I will file a claim for compensation for mental damage’
Even these bloody phrases
As you write
When I think about it
Actually, it would be easier to talk about.
If you look at the proof of contents,
As you know
I am in every situation
acted lawfully
Legally receive power of attorney
legally own a house
I was trying to sell it
Your client
I used an expedient method to block it.
And that too on the day of the contract.
Thanks to this, time and financial losses are
I'm very bored
I wrote in the proof of contents
Everything as it is
We plan to implement it quickly.
No more buyers
I can't make you wait, so
But on the day of the sale
Have you checked the certified copy of the register?
This is a large amount of money being exchanged.
When signing a contract
prepare in advance
It's better to do it thoroughly.
You were a little underprepared.
A copy of the register every day
Has anyone confirmed this?
But if you checked it every day
Until the damage is very severe
I don't think you went
First of all, I will convey it that way.
Is there anything else you want to say?
Hmm
I took out my favorite hammer drill.
If you tell Baek Do-ha, he will know.
This is limited
This is the model I wanted to get.
I'm going to use it today
Let's go there
Bench press and hockey saturation
Selling it on the second hand market
Please tell me
There is no space at home
Ah!
And child support
Tell them to send some more
If I tell you, you will understand.
Did you two have children?
Did you ever have kids?
You said
Hello? Baek Do-ha?
Are you listening?
Ah, yes, I'm listening.
Before I break through all the walls
I guess I should go see it.
Because he’s the kind of kid who does it if he wants to.
- Oh, and again...
-After that
Ah
my things
I guess they said they would sell it all.
Well, a hockey stick or something.
Yes, you said exactly that.
Oh, and child support too.
You told me to send you 200,000 won more?
It's really still the same
Okay, I'll get back to you.
Where are you going?
- uh? Village hall.
-Why?
Oh, I want you to sign this consent form.
All the residents are gathered together.
That's only Director Song
You're doing it alone.
Ah...
Our team's work
First of all, isn't it important?
Let's go, get some summer guests.
Why isn't it coming?
Oh, come on! ah!
Oh, what should I do! Oh, what should I do, my eyes!
Fighting
Ah, mom! mom
Mom, Mom! mom!
Mom, what should I do, what should I do!
Just go home! Get off work!
Ah...
I really want to go home
Ha...
Ugh, noisy!
huh?
what?
Watermelon!
I'm here, Song Subak!
Song watermelon!
watermelon?
Ha, Mr.
After...
- Hello?
- Hey, write.
Did you come to my house today?
-There is no watermelon.
- No
- Can’t find everything?
- Yes
What should I do?
Shall we go and look for it together?
Just hang up
Watermelon!
Ha, Mr.
Grandma, haven’t you seen the watermelon?
Uh, I didn't see it.
What's going on?
Uh, I don't know, I wonder where it went
Watermelon!
Song watermelon!
uh?
Watermelon!
Watermelon
Ha...
Hey, watermelon
- Did you get scammed again?
- what?
Hey, I pay child support every month.
They send it to me regularly like that.
Why is the watermelon so skinny?
ha
Ugh
- Hey! Hey, watermelon!
- As expected
This damn summer is unlucky
Well...
Come here!
Hey, you...
After...
Hey
I'll give you turkey chews
I'll give you two, two, okay?
let's go
Let's go, let's go, let's go
After...
Hey, really
No Turkey Chew, you fooled me.
This is our teacher.
Because you betrayed me too, tsk
Lift your feet
Why are you following him and me?
I should have bitten it off
Huh? You traitor
Ugh
Ha...
I really want you...
Hey!
- Oh, it's pretty.
- Hey!
Watermelon come here, you really...
Hey, hey
If you show off like this
Who would be so upset, huh?
your mom
Don’t you know that the back end is secretly long?
Hey, Song Ha-kyung
send me your statement
I sent him 500,000 won every month.
Why do you need more money?
Hey
You have a taste for watermelon
Do you know how high-end it is?
The price of Türkiye Chew goes up every day.
Hey, you’re going for a haircut, right?
It's sad that my dog is an old dog.
Receive additional fees
They charge extra money
Do you know parenting?
There is no choice with 500,000 won.
you wipe your feet
Hey, why is it 500,000 won? you?
I take care of him 24 hours a day.
I take a walk for 2 hours every day
Necessary nutrients regularly
Buy it, take it to the hospital
my labor fee
Don’t you know it’s more than 500,000 won?
It's still the same
What are you looking at?
Tsk
Song Ha-kyung
It's been a while, we
It's been 2 years, right?
Stop it
We're doing Tiki Taka like this
I know it's not
Sit down, I have something to say.
Did you hire a lawyer?
After 2 years, someone sent me a certificate of contents
Uncle told me
Don’t you know I handed over the power of attorney?
Don't you know that you handed it over to me again?
While you were living a leisurely life in America
Going back and forth to Korea
I guess you don't know
This real estate market is very
It has changed, and Patan-myeon too.
If you miss these people now
I don't know when it will be sold again
Maybe it won't sell forever
Three generations living together
They seem like good people, I want to sell
So?
Because you'll be busy
All you have to do is hand over your seal and consent form.
It's complicated and difficult
I'll take care of everything
why are you like that
Do you want to sell this house?
The reason is
Don’t you know best?
I don't know if you know
If you don't sell it now
Another 5 years, maybe 10 years
If you can't keep selling it, you have to be stuck.
Aren’t you sick of this place?
- Yes
- But why don’t you come just once?
I told you not to come
If you come in front of me one more time
He said he would kill me
But why did you come here, huh?
ha
I'm really going crazy because of you
If you don't show up
He said he was going to drill into my wall
That's my hockey club.
How much do I care?
He said he would sell it used.
I like people this much
You come and I come
Go and go then
When I tell it to turn off, it turns off.
Since I summon you like this again, I get summoned.
None of us have changed, right?
Sounds exciting?
Yeah, a while ago
I bought my own house
So, after two years, Song Ha-kyung
Mix words with me
Good
But I have to wash up first.
I came right from the scene
What?
Hey
Who are you to come in here?
Are you even going to take a bath?
why?
I said I would wash at my house.
When you say good things, go to Seoul
Get out of my sight, okay?
you keep begging me
Don't you think they're chasing you?
- Hey, Baek Do-ha.
- But Song Ha-kyung
what are you doing again
He did something ridiculous
- What?
- You are now
They say they are in the business of tearing down fences.
That's architecturally
Do you think it makes sense?
What are you? How did you know?
Are you my stalker?
Hey, just walking around Patan-myeon
It's all about you
Well, the king of civil complaints, Dr. Song.
I was demoted after being criticized by my boss.
A big liver
Of course it's Song Ha-kyung.
Hey
do you want to die
You really want to get beat up, huh?
I thought something had changed
As expected, as expected
That too
Something I've heard quite a few times now
It's the same, just do it one more time
What are you going to do?
you're so cool
Are you saying you want to bleed with me?
Once or twice
Did you see the blood between us?
Huh
The number of birds you haven’t seen has increased a lot.
This Tiki Taka
Is that the only thing that has increased?
What else has increased?
Everything you imagine
Fortunately, nothing has changed
This neighborhood and this house
Song Ha-kyung also lived here.
I've changed a bit
Please take care of me in the future, Song Ha-kyung
Ha...
What is it?
If I open it now, I’m going to get hit, right?
It was almost a KO, but I was crushed.
He has been
What happened, Mr. Lee?
Oh, Mr.
Has nothing changed, pervert?
Right up to the wall in front of you
You need to increase the waterproofing.
Ah, like that every time
What if you do it roughly?
Hey, they're all veterans
At this level, the waterproofing will not break.
Dubber is dying
When, huh? drawing report
In what time period, huh? Filled with silicone
Ah...
What if I draw it for you?
uh?
hello
Hello, hello, yes
Boy, I heard it
If you do waterproofing on the roof layer like that,
The waterproof layer is all broken, huh?
Process the floor *
150, protruding part
Main 3,000*
Now, just look at this and do it.
And if you are a veteran
field books
You should have known everything
I followed the director to the scene.
Do you draw it every time?
I got it, you idiot.
every time I work
Do you know how unlucky you really are?
Now, now, now
Okay, let's do it this way.
Man, if you don't do this
This guy can draw 100 more pictures.
Oh my, ignore it.
- Come on, let's go!
- Gassey
- Fighting, fighting
- Man
- When did you come?
- I just got here.
Not yet
Rather than calling to get a loan
Ha-kyung is getting more phone calls.
What are you going to do about that house?
I have an idea
Are you really not trying to sell that house?
Is that why you asked for a name?
If it wasn't for that house
Song Ha-kyung of the world
Can you contact me?
Oh my, what should I do, you guys
No, more than that, Dad.
Have you read the contest draft I sent?
- That's why I came.
- Oh, that's right.
What are you doing?
Are you really going to do that?
Uh, I'm going to try it.
How about from an expert's point of view?
Do you think it will work?
Ah...
fence teardown project
This is a pain, huh?
Now, if you get consent from residents,
I think I'll get started
The problem is the upcoming heavy rain advisory.
All the residents
Because you are afraid of floods
Director Song?
yes
Hmm, yes
Ah, but
Well, you know, Mr.
The drainage system was completed two years ago.
Discharge from the dam and water resources corporation
As long as you don't change it you'll be fine
So even if you tear down the wall
There is no flood
Oh, so the consent form
how can i get it
I have to go back with the mayor.
no, sir
Why, why do you suddenly change your words?
Ah, when I explained it to you last time
You said it was good that the road was widened.
Ah, it's the rainy season soon.
There needs to be a wall to prevent flood damage.
Don’t you remember 3 years ago?
Could it be because of the fence?
in the sky like that
If there's a puncture or it spills
Even Seoul is not safe.
Ah, it was cheap.
Haha! Look at this, this
Oh my, I like it so much
No, if you break the wall
When the dam burst, we Kkokkos
They say it's all floating away
Oh, who is it, Grandma?
modern drainage system
How well is it?
kid, that
Director Baek said that, so solve it quickly.
- Major General Baek?
- Yes
What does that mean?
Director Baek is over there in Namhae.
Yes, that's right, Director Baek's son Naemi
It was like that, right?
- That's right.
- Aig
my son said that
Did your son do that?
Ugh
The bean sprouts are trimmed well.
Have you tried a lot?
where a lot
It's a skill I've tried
No, grandmothers.
How is Pathan these days?
Isn’t the waterlogging bad?
Right
It's been a while since there was an uproar
That was all 10 years ago
It's because these walls are being repaired.
Oh, right
Ah, that and above
living in the same house
The architects
What did you do for me
That's right, grandma
At that time, I changed all the walls.
There is less flooding than in the past.
Oh my, are you drawing it?
Oh, then you can't break down the wall.
Why break something that was made strong?
Why did you destroy something that was fine?
Not behind
That wouldn't work, I didn't know
Wow, at the awards ceremony
It was you too
Talking nonsense to seniors
The neighborhood is low
You probably don't know
So?
It's downstream from the dam.
If it rains, will the flood damage be severe?
Yeah, I know.
So the walls in this neighborhood
With my dad, uncle, and aunt
It hasn't been completely renovated.
Ha...
Rainwater thanks to these fences
It went away well so there was less flooding.
stop
not good business
Hey, that's art through architecture.
That's your hypothesis
As an architectural civil servant, my hypothesis is different.
I'm not sure what I'm trying to tear down
No, it's the external walls on the side of the road.
If you get rid of it, there won't be a flood.
I'll prove it to you
Well, how can you prove it?
More, more, more, more, more
How, Dr. Song?
Destroy more?
Yes, sir.
Please be more merciless.
Okay, more! Brother, more!
Oh, what are you, there are too many
Now
If you tear it all down
This summer will end too
Huh? Uh, not there!
Oh my, oh my
- Huh? Stop!
- Not there, stop!
-Only the outside wall!
- Stop, stop!
Stop! stop!
Outside fence...
Ha...
Director Song
What should I do with this now?
child
I am that fence and this fence
I thought I was just going to destroy everything.
That guy can't hear...
I'm sorry, really.
Okay, how do I fix it first?
Let's discuss
Aww, teacher
Just do this so recklessly
What if I destroy everything?
Already a heavy rain warning
In the hot season, wow
Ha, when everyone tells you not to do that.
Don't do it
Ah, our myeon office
The most rational person
Why are you like that these days?
Because I will take responsibility for everything.
So how are you going to take responsibility?
Even the inner wall collapsed
Song Jumugwan's guide
I won't be able to survive this rainy season now.
Then, to the house below and the house next door.
It all affects
It's not like you don't know.
Already due to flood damage
These people have a lot of trauma.
If there is a complaint against us due to this...
There is no heavy rain warning yet.
Before that I
I'll solve it somehow
So how?
How, what are you going to do?
First of all, what's left of the clapboard
I'll borrow a water pump and solve the problem.
How are you going to do that on your own?
- Let me help you.
- Oh my?
catch
here
Hey, I'll do it alone.
you just go
This is enough, thank you
Oh, stop it and go.
I'm not helping you, huh?
I'm fixing up my house
My house is ruined because of you
Hey
Are you laughing at me now?
To be honest
no
I'm dying of pity
Song Ha-kyung
I guess I can't do it
I can't sell my house
Ha...
you say that now
Do you want to do this in this situation?
Because this is the situation
Doing it now
Then
I guess I'll have no choice but to sue.
Then do it
If you have no choice but to do that
I thought it would be like this too
Summer is always for me
They only give me the worst like this
Oh, this is a bucket of cement.
It will take a while to dry
Let's try anyway, okay?
Yes, please, sir.
Yes, but it won't be easy
What is my summer like?
Where did it all get so twisted?
fact
i know the answer
Everything
It's because of the damn Baek Do-ha.
Always here, right? Song Ha-kyung?
Even if I get a little angry, I blurt it out like this
maybe I expected it
The moment that bastard appears in my life
always
It's going to be a mess
Ash tree
By growing it big
We're going to build a tree house on top of it.
Hey, to grow a tree
It will take more than 10 years
Who is going up?
you and me
What do you say?
It's not even the rainy season
The summer when rainbows bloomed
Ah!
Oh my! i won
So much so that I can't hear any other sounds
summer with heavy rain
Look look
- Oh, what should I do?
- Let's go home first.
2012, bare body
The summer that endured the monsoon rain
One, two, three!
Even the starlight in the night sky
A stinging summer
2014, finally
A summer that was crazy due to heat stroke
speak up
Say something, Baek Do-ha.
Say something!
At least make an excuse!
you go away
Let's never see each other again
You bastard
And in 2022
It didn't even rain
A summer that soaked both body and mind
yes
I thought of everything
I had it frozen in the refrigerator.
Because of the midsummer heat
It all melted
I hate summer so much
I wanted to run away from summer
All my summers are full of white peaches
What happens that summer
Because there wasn't one
Song Ha-kyung
Do you still hate me that much?
In summer
always had no luck
Because in the summer
Because Baek Doha is coming
and
My summer again this year
I guess I'll be so unlucky
Why did you come back?
Are you finally curious about that?
Shall I tell you?
Baek Do-ha said something
Did you hire a lawyer?
What are the conditions and purpose?
Baek Do-ha
About Song Ha-kyung
I guess you really don't know anything.
Song Ha-kyung, should I give this house to you?
Get out!
Don't come in
2 years ago
A shameless bastard like you
They should have been charged with fraud.
Our 17 years of memories to you
Are these all things that will disappear if you sell your house?
Why are these two like that?
Are you obsessed with peanut restaurants?
I'm terrible!
I'm so sick of it!
Lie
You can't beat me this time
I have no intention of losing to you.
Let’s go somewhere
Let's end it in the mud
That's for us
I think it's a more fitting ending